edmhunters.com 2017-01-19

# Privacy Policy | EDM Hunters

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which EDM Hunters collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.edmhunters.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by EDM Hunters.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

We may store additional information about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, if you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a service that helps us see how our site is being used. Google Analytics uses cookies. Google Analytics also relies on JavaScript, which most browsers allow you to disable. Google Analytics collects information such as your IP address, which browser and operating system you are using and which site referred you to our site. This information is transmitted to Google where we access it in aggregated form. We do not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information and we do not share any of this information with any third parties. We use the data to help us analyse how our website is being used. For example we can tell from which part of the world most of our visitors are coming from and which websites are referring them to us.

This site also uses Google Analytics Advertising Features including Demographics and Interest reporting, Remarketing, GDN Impression Reporting, and the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. This site and third-party vendors use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie). Users can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertiser Features, including through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI's consumer opt-out).

How we use collected information

EDM Hunters may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To improve customer service - Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To improve our Site - We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Security

We uses industry standard measures to protect the personal information that is stored in our database. We restrict access to your personal information to employees that need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. However, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Changes to this privacy policy

EDM Hunters has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us using the contact form.

This document was last updated on February 27, 2015
